The letter that arrived for Marie
from Baron Shaderan and his wife...
You good-for-nothing with your hideous red
hair, apologize to Anastasia and die!
Her mother writes nothing
but horribly abusive words.
And her father...
Marie, why haven't you returned?
Your work is here in this
house! Come back at once!
The opinions of husband
and wife appear to clash.
Would parents really tyrannize
their own child this much?
Mio, while I'm gone, I'd like
you to investigate something.
Understood.
A month has passed since the knights'
festival that struck like a storm.
Episode 6 "Am I Enough As I Am?"
The weather is so lovely!
Today seems like it will be a good day!
Good morning, my lady.
Are you already awake?
Good morning. Yes, I'm already awake.
I win today, Wolfgang.
It appears that you've beaten me.
Marie! Morning!
Come now, Cillie.
I do apologize. My granddaughter
is still just an apprentice.
It's all right. Please don't worry.
Good morning, Caecilie.
Look! Tunika gave me buns!
Am I cute?
Yes, very. I've never seen any girl
they suited so well before.
Right?
I'll do your hair like this too, Marie.
Mio has other business again
today, so I'm your attendant!
Thank you.
By the way, my lady...
what will you be wearing today?
Let's see. Today...
What do you think?
Marie, you're so cute!
You are truly beautiful.
If the master were to see you, he'd
embrace you before even realizing it.
L-Lately, it's so strange...
When I think of Lord Kyros, my heart...
Marie, hurry up! Hurry up!
My lady, where are you
going in such a hurry?
Lunch isn't for a while yet.
It isn't that, Toppo. You see, today is...
The day the master comes home!
Then, today you'll be eating your
parfait with the master, won't you?
My lady!
Take these with you.
Let's go, Marie!
Thank you, Johan.
Count Kyros Granado has returned!
I'm back, Marie.
W-Welcome home.
What are those flowers?
I think they're damask roses.
Johan told me to bring
them. Do you like them?
They aren't for me.
They're an accessory for you, Marie.
Though, in a way, they are
a present for me as well.
You are like a flower personified.
I nearly embraced you
without even realizing it.
Marie, your face is steaming!
Please don't mention that.
May I?
What? Oh, the bouquet.
Please do.
P-Please, don't tease me like that!
I am not teasing you.
You have grown even more beautiful.
I-I just know he's teasing me.
I thought we'd have dinner together,
but he's already gone out again.
The betrothal ceremony is coming
together nicely, but I'm still nervous.
Aside from helping my father and
the things I learned in school...
I don't know anything.
It's at times like this...
"The Tale of the Raggedy Red Cat."
I often read this when I
felt anxious, didn't I?
My lady, wouldn't it be better
to do this tomorrow morning?
I'm sorry.
Once I've found out how to
bind this book, I'll go back.
What's this?
I thought I heard footsteps, and now...
I-It has been quite some time, Lady Liu Liu.
Miss Marie! It has been a while, hasn't it?
What's wrong? Are you looking
for something so late at night?
Yes. My book has fallen to pieces,
and I'd like to mend it.
Well, please come in.
This is incredible!
It's like a dream!
You must like books.
I do. Do you like them too, Lady Liu Liu?
I'm here for research.
My spelling in Diltzian is still shaky.
Is that... a letter?
Isn't there anyone you can
ask to write it for you?
Kyros is very busy,
so he's asked me to help him.
That is an invitation to attend
the betrothal ceremony, you see.
It must be written by the couple in
question, or someone close to them.
Um, would it be wrong for me to write them?
What? You'd do that?
That would be such a help!
These are for people in
Ipsandros, so I'll write them.
I can do the ones in Ipsian, too.
What? Miss Marie, you understand Ipsian?
Yes, but only to read and write,
and for everyday conversation.
The lady loves Ipsandrian stories.
She came here to mend this book.
The Raggedy Red Cat?
Oh, how nostalgic!
My older sister read it to me when I was
little. It's a book I love very much.
And my sister seems to have learned
Ipsian from our late grandmother.
What a well-learned grandmother.
My father says she was an eccentric
layabout who studied foreign languages.
Women don't need academics!
The reason my mother was
alone and without charm
was all due to her dabbling in academics!
What's that supposed to mean?
A clever woman who knows other languages...
She'd be quite the catch for merchants
and the nobility, wouldn't she?
What?
Though, Ipsian isn't very practical unless
you are engaged in trade with them.
Flarian and Shainan on the other hand...
I speak those!
Though I studied them both on my own.
Really?
Miss Marie, you're the daughter
of a baron, aren't you?
Many of the tenant farmers on
Shaderan lands are immigrants,
so knowing foreign languages is
essential to properly manage things.
And you did all that, Miss Marie?
Even though it's incredibly
important work for a baron?
Y-Yes.
Oh, but my father put together
the management plans.
I only really assisted in simple matters.
"Assisted in simple matters," you say?
Y-Yes. I love to write letters.
Even though I wrote
on someone else's behalf,
it allowed me to converse
with someone as an equal.
What beautiful handwriting.
You clearly put a lot
of heart into that letter.
Sign it with your own name, please.
What? Are you certain?
Of course.
You didn't write that on my behalf.
You're the one who composed
those lovely words, Miss Marie.
My own...
Now that you mention it, I did... didn't I?
You know...
To be honest, I didn't expect much from you.
I heard that you were a noble daughter from
the countryside who hadn't entered society.
But you were the first person
Kyros ever proposed to...
and a long time ago, a lot
of people helped me, too.
I thought that I'd help you
wherever you might be lacking.
I'm so sorry!
But I take it all back!
I'm so happy that you'll be my son's wife!
I've come to love you!
I am an imperfect mother,
but I hope we'll get along well.
I-I'm so sorry!
It isn't what you think!
Don't worry. It's all right.
Cry as much as you like.
I wasn't sad at all, but for some
reason, my tears just wouldn't stop.
I cried like a baby.
Welcome home, Master.
Before you go and see Lady Marie...
may I have a moment of your time?
I've finished investigating the
matter you inquired about.
Marie really is the daughter
of the baron and his wife.
Everyone in the Shaderan
family is related by blood.
Are you certain about these results?
Yes, sir.
The records of noble family trees kept
safe in the Royal Palace Library
show no evidence of an adopted
child or remarriage.
Could the baron have
forced himself on a maid?
Or his wife could have had an affair.
These records come from the royal
capital's maternity hospitals.
Records of the births
of Marie and Anastasia?
The younger brother was born at home,
but Lady Elvira definitely
gave birth to the sisters.
How did she seem at the time?
I was told that both parents
shed tears of joy.
Could there have been
a mix-up at the hospital?
It's a small hospital with just one bed.
I believe the chances of
that are incredibly slim.
Then the people who spew these cursed
words at her are her actual parents?
Master, if it were human nature for parents
to love their children unconditionally,
and to protect them through anything,
then I would not be here.
I was told that this arrived this morning.
"Father on his deathbed. Return at once."
This is basically a threat.
If she sees this, I believe that Lady
Marie will return to her parents' house.
What can I do to protect Marie?
And even if I can protect her, keeping her
locked in this fortress like it's a birdcage...
Would that bring her happiness?
Miss Marie, drop your hips straight down.
Do not forget to smile.
Yes, my lady!
Emotions are key to a curtsy.
If you show them respect without expressing
a feeling of welcome, then there's no point!
Yes, my lady!
Is she being bullied by her
future mother-in-law?!
Liu Liu, what are you doing?!
Oh, Lord Kyros! Welcome home!
Kyros! You've arrived at the perfect
time. Be her practice partner.
Practice partner?
That's right. For when Miss Marie has
to meet royalty and other nobility.
What? I told you that you don't have
to make her do any of this, didn't I?
You and I can handle all of that
at the betrothal ceremony.
Marie has never been
introduced into society!
That's why she's practicing.
It'll be fine. Miss Marie is clever,
and she has an aptitude for this.
Her posture is quite nice, too.
I trained by chopping wood.
I see. That's why your figure is so stylish.
Oh, but it isn't!
I wanted Marie to be able to
dress in beautiful things,
and to help her live a happy,
peaceful life, but...
Master!
Marie's curtsy is really stylish!
Is it?
Thank you so much for coming to
celebrate the two of us today.
And it isn't just the etiquette
involved in greetings!
Miss Marie wrote all the
thank you letters, too.
Why are you working her so hard?
That makes us no different
from the Shaderan—
Son, remember this.
Love and overprotectiveness
are not the same.
Women are not baby birds.
Don't trap her in a cage. Make sure
she has the chance to take flight.
Um, did I do it well?
Yes. It was irreproachable. Truly lovely.
You've worked hard.
Yes, I have!
The first time I met her...
she smiled that same way.
Now then!
Shall we take a little break?
Let's all have tea together.
Yay! Snacks!
I want to eat something sweet.
Indeed! I'm sure Toppo will have
something prepared for us.
Wait, Marie.
Hooray!
There's something I have to tell you.
Me?
This is from your father.
I'm sorry, but I worry about you
returning alone. I'll go with—
There's no need for me to return.
What?
Because this is a lie.
This is my father's handwriting.
A person supposedly on
his deathbed wrote this.
By chance, have other
demanding letters arrived?
That's...
Thank you.
They must have had truly
sickening things written in them,
and you protected me, didn't you?
No, I'm sorry for acting
without your permission.
Hiring people would cost money.
I'm sure he has work that he
wants to foist off on me.
It isn't that he wants to see me.
Marie...
My parents hate me, don't they?
The way they yelled at me all the time...
they weren't disciplining me.
Before, no matter how
much Marie was bullied,
she thought it was natural because she
thought she wasn't lovely, but now...
You've grown so strong, Marie.
It's all thanks to the people here in
the palace, and to you, Lord Kyros.
Thank you for treating me with such care.
Lord Kyros?
I-I'm sorry!
Y-Yes. Not at all.
My lady, your dress today
is lovely, as usual.
Thank you. Cillie picked it out for me.
Right? She's so cute!
The way this is going, I can also...
Marie!
You look adorable.
SILENCE...
Wh-Why?
Does she hate me?
I-I'm sorry.
I-I'm not accustomed to hearing
such things from gentlemen.
I see. I'm sorry for making you nervous.
And now, everyone!
A blueberry tart!
Hooray!
It looks delicious!
Oh, my lady! That dress is incredible!
Really? Thank you!
Why? Toppo is a man, too.
She already treats everyone
else as family, but...
Is it because I've been away so much?
Marie, I will stay by your
side from now on, so—
Oh, Mio!
You're back. Welcome home.
Yes. I apologize for any trouble
my absence may have caused you.
Master, I'm terribly sorry to
interrupt while you are relaxing...
What is it?
I would like to request a leave of absence.
There is somewhere rather
remote that I would like to visit.
Oh no! But you've only just returned!
I'm so sorry, Lady Marie.
But even I have someone
I want to go and see.
Oh, how lovely! I'm sorry for saying
anything that might keep you from going.
Not at all. It made me happy to hear it.
Lady Marie, with the betrothal
ceremony drawing near,
please take some time
to bond privately with the master.
Y-Yes, you're right. I'll do my best.
What is all that?
It's for Baron Shaderan and his wife.
I stressed that they are not allowed
to speak badly of my wife,
and I wrote out all of Marie's
lovely qualities in detail.
What are you doing with yourself?
If by chance you see the
baron where you're going,
I thought you could clobber him with it.
Well, well.
Use this.
And use the palace carriage, too.
Also, take at least one attendant with you.
I'm quite strong.
I know.
I want someone with you so that you
don't have to use that strength.
Don't take the villain's role, Mio.
Um, why am I here...
Miss Mio?
The master told me to bring someone.
B-But isn't this a bad idea?
You're going to see your
sweetheart, aren't you?
If I really were seeing a
sweetheart, then it would be bad.
Then, is it a friend?
Miss Mio, you have friends?
The legends of your homeland, Louhav Island,
say that anyone who dies
before the age of eighteen
can travel to paradise, without exception.
Congrats! Have a nice trip!
I'm sorry! I don't want to die!
You're meant to ward off bandits.
There was a tragic accident
here two months ago, you see.
An accident two months ago?
Oh, are you traveling to the Shaderan lands?
What's this?
"Big sis, come home. Elder
sister is already home."
Big sis, come home.
Elder sister is already home.
From Cedric
"From Cedric."
Who's Cedric?
Lady Marie's younger brother
who turns six this year.
A letter was included in
the package we received earlier.
What? But Lady Marie's older
sister passed away, didn't she?
Her carriage fell from a cliff
with her inside, didn't it?
No.
According to a more detailed investigation,
they were attacked by
bandits on the flatlands,
and as they fled along the river, the
carriage overturned in the muddy waters.
Then, is it possible...
The river water was cold, and the rain from
the previous day had caused it to swell.
Rescuing anyone who fell
in would be impossible.
Y-Yes, you're right.
But if that's true...
then what about this letter?
Oh, your hair is as beautiful as silk.
My lovely, lovely Anastasia.
This is Tomas.
Doing as Miss Mio said and setting
out on a journey is fine with me,
but I never imagined things
would turn out like this.
Miss Mio has me dancing to her tune. I feel
like my life has gotten shorter because of it.
Next time, "You're So Close, I
Think You May Make Me Dizzy."
Episode 7 "You're So Close, I
Think You May Make Me Dizzy"
I'm begging you. Please watch, won't you?